[{"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "Which device was patented in 1970 by  Douglas Engelbart, an American inventor of Norwegian descent?", "correct_answer": "The computer mouse", "incorrect_answers": ["The traffic light", "The internal combustion engine", "The can opener"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "In the movie The Crow, the wedding ring Eric was looking for was hidden where in Gideons pawn shop?", "correct_answer": "In the metal box underneath the shelf", "incorrect_answers": ["In the back room", "In a pouch on the wall", "In a secret niche in the floor"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "Who portrays Alan Stanwyk in the movie Fletch?", "correct_answer": "Tim Matheson", "incorrect_answers": ["George Wendt", "M. Emmet Walsh", "Chevy Chase"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "Which statement is true about airplanes?", "correct_answer": "To dive, elevators are down.", "incorrect_answers": ["To dive, elevators are up.", "To dive, ailerons are down.", "To dive, ailerons are up."]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "Who is the director of the 2002 science fiction movie Minority Report that starred Tom Cruise and Colin Farrell?", "correct_answer": "Steven Spielberg", "incorrect_answers": ["Martin Scorsese", "Robert Zemeckis", "Oliver Stone"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "Apart from the American cockroach, what other cockroach species is among the best-known pests?", "correct_answer": "All of these", "incorrect_answers": ["Oriental cockroach", "Asian cockroach", "German cockroach"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "Why is Blue Ray better than Red Ray/Laser?", "correct_answer": "It can read more memory.", "incorrect_answers": ["It is stronger.", "It gets damaged less.", "It has more memory."]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "What is another name for a nutria?", "correct_answer": "Coypu", "incorrect_answers": ["Beaver", "Muskrat", "Rat"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "Can a beaver hold its breath underwater for more than 30 minutes?", "correct_answer": "No", "incorrect_answers": ["Yes"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "Walt Disneys 1942 animated movie Bambi caused a phenomenon called the Bambi effect. What is it related to?", "correct_answer": "Feeling sympathy for animals", "incorrect_answers": ["Orphaned children", "Men who get overly emotional", "Children who become independent at young age"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "What actress received the Golden Raspberry Award for Worst Actress for her performance in the 1984 movie Bolero?", "correct_answer": "Bo Derek", "incorrect_answers": ["Brooke Shields", "Sharon Stone", "Kim Basinger"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "Humans are the only species that make love face-to-face.", "correct_answer": "False", "incorrect_answers": ["True"]}]